Text,Entities
"We have a new name, but a legacy of serving the aerospace industry for over 50 years. Mires Machining, a CNC machine shop founded in 1966 is now DL Dynamic.","[('over 50 years', 'QUANTITY'), ('Mires Machining', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('1966', 'DATE'), ('DL Dynamic', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Coevolve is a leading global provider of Integrated SD-WAN and Cloud Networking solutions, with clients in over 75 countries on 6 continents.","[('Coevolve', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('SD-WAN', 'OTHER'), ('Networking', 'OTHER'), ('over 75 countries', 'QUANTITY'), ('6 continents', 'QUANTITY')]"
Exeter Homes Visalia Real Estate Tulare County Investment Property Darcy Staberg | DS Realty Inc investors commercial lots land ranches single family homes,"[('Exeter Homes', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Visalia Real Estate', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Tulare', 'LOCATION'), ('Darcy Staberg', 'PERSON'), ('DS Realty Inc', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Shop powered by PrestaShop,"[('PrestaShop', 'TITLE')]"
Color hex encyclopedia providing information about any color.,[]
"We stop process and document fraud. Our secure technologies are at the forefront of security innovations, providing multiple layers of security, process efficiency and flexibility.",[]
"Lumivo is a leading global digital research agency specializing in online 
and mobile competitive benchmarking. We help our clients to measure and 
improve their online user experience (UX) and digital effectiveness. The 
Lumivo team have helped over 100 leading brands, including eBay, Sony, 
IKEA, Hertz, Mastercard, Barclaycard and Vodafone.","[('Lumivo', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Lumivo', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('over 100 leading brands', 'QUANTITY'), ('eBay', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Sony', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('IKEA', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hertz', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Mastercard', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Barclaycard', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Vodafone', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"MUN is highly-effective, natural, anti-aging and brightening skin care based on pristine healing botanicals, produced and sourced with integrity. Try MUN products like Akanri Serum, Anarose Toner, and Akwi Cleanser with 10% off your first order. Free shipping $75+.","[('MUN', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('MUN', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Akanri', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Serum', 'COMMERCIAL_ITEM'), ('Anarose Toner', 'COMMERCIAL_ITEM'), ('Akwi Cleanser', 'COMMERCIAL_ITEM'), ('10%', 'QUANTITY'), ('first order', 'QUANTITY'), ('$75+', 'QUANTITY')]"
The best agency in the world.,[]
"IT Convergence is a top Oracle cloud managed services provider with offerings across migration, hosting, integration, IaaS, PaaS, SaaS, Analytics, Training, Testing and Change Management","[('Convergence', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Oracle', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"GEM Advanced Magnetometers is a renowned supplier of magnetometers, gradiometers and magnetic sensors for earth science, geophysics and other applications.","[('GEM Advanced', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Magnetometers', 'COMMERCIAL_ITEM')]"
"Rydalmere’s favourite with great food restaurant & bar offering steaks, pub 
classics, pastas & pizzas & much more. Make a reservation now!","[('Rydalmere', 'LOCATION')]"
"AEI Lighting is a manufacturer & solutions provider of LED, Induction, T5 / T5HO, T8 & Skylight lighting for industrial, commercial & retail applications","[('AEI Lighting', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Sutera Energy Solutions is a Sub-Surface Consulting & Capability Development Service Provider, specializing in Well Completions, Production Enhancement, and Unconventional Shale.","[('Sutera Energy Solutions', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Factory for Sale Malaysia | Warehouse for sale Malaysia| Industrial land for Sale Malaysia,"[('Malaysia', 'LOCATION'), ('Malaysia', 'LOCATION'), ('Malaysia', 'LOCATION')]"
"We pride ourselves in designing and offering products and services that meet the needs of organizations in the inter-related fields of knowledge management, development communications, monitoring and evaluation, and research and learning.",[]
"Watch Netflix films & TV programmes online or stream right to your smart TV, game console, PC, Mac, mobile, tablet and more.","[('Netflix', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Mac', 'COMMERCIAL_ITEM')]"
"CJX is a professional information technology and information security incident response company founded by experienced network security, architecture and investigations practitioners. The partners’ experience includes years of successful investigations and recovery after cyber incidents. We specialize in response to malware; advanced, persistent threats (APT); botnets; and remote-access Trojan attacks. We investigate attacks on-premise, in-the-cloud, and…","[('CJX', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"coinmaster free spins,,coinmaster free rewards,static moon games,free spins and coins,free cards,coinmaster free spins and cards,coinmaster free cards","[('coinmaster', 'TITLE'), ('coinmaster', 'TITLE'), ('coinmaster', 'COMMERCIAL_ITEM'), ('coinmaster', 'COMMERCIAL_ITEM')]"
"T&N by Sagar. Comfortable Designer Ballet Flats. Made of the finest 
leathers that lend to luxurious comfort & fitted with a unique footprint 
sole, these ballet flats are truly one of a kind. Where have you left your 
footprint today?","[('T&N', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Sagar', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('one', 'QUANTITY'), ('today', 'DATE')]"
"Profound Strength: combining strength & conditioning to make every athlete, better.","[('every athlete', 'QUANTITY')]"
Just another WordPress site,"[('WordPress', 'TITLE')]"
All sports news around the world,"[('All', 'QUANTITY')]"
"SkyScope is Transport Canada certified aerial photographers based in 
Victoria BC. Turnkey drone services for a unique and informative look at 
your business.","[('SkyScope', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Transport Canada', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Victoria BC', 'LOCATION')]"
"View Hon Kee Restaurant BBQ Menu, June, 2021 coupons, HonKee argyle online order, Order Delivery from honkee argyle menu, hon kee bbq, hon kee restaurant menu, best BBQ restaurant in Argyle Chicago, IL, best peking duck chicago, best bbq in chicago, best roasted pig, Chicago Chinese food, Chicago Chinese cuisine, uptown Chicago Chinese bbq, Chicago Chinese bbq, best wonton noodle soup Chicago","[('Hon Kee Restaurant', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('June, 2021', 'DATE'), ('HonKee argyle', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('honkee argyle', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('hon kee bbq', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('hon kee restaurant', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Argyle Chicago, IL', 'LOCATION'), ('chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chicago', 'OTHER'), ('Chinese', 'OTHER'), ('Chicago', 'OTHER'), ('Chinese', 'OTHER'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION'), ('Chinese', 'OTHER'), ('Chicago', 'OTHER'), ('Chinese', 'OTHER'), ('Chicago', 'LOCATION')]"
"Fashion Touch is an online women's fashion store. We have good prices on the items you are looking for. You can buy shoes, dresses, skirts, sunglasses and handbags bodysuits, blouses, belts, necklaces with the moment trends. Remember... Always in fashion with Fashion Touch.","[('Fashion Touch', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Fashion Touch', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Please enter your slogan here!,[]
"All our watches go through a high-quality evaluation and certification process by our certified watchmakers, which includes:Quality inspectionAuthenticity","[('All our watches', 'QUANTITY')]"
"Carpet shop in Singapore for exhibition carpet, office carpet, carpet tile, Artificial grass carpet, vinyl floor, sisal carpet, flame retardant fabric | Curtex Pte Ltd","[('Singapore', 'LOCATION'), ('Curtex Pte Ltd', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Specification Lighting Sales, also known as SLS, brings premier lighting manufacturers to the New York design community.","[('Sales', 'TITLE'), ('SLS', 'TITLE'), ('New York', 'LOCATION')]"
"Atos is a global leader in digital transformation with 110,000 employees and annual revenue of € 12 billion.","[('Atos', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('110,000 employees', 'QUANTITY'), ('annual', 'QUANTITY'), ('€ 12 billion', 'QUANTITY')]"
Orchid and Fern Nursery,[]
"Aggregate Resources.  Southwest Michigan's Choice for Sand, Stone and Portable Crushing.  Call 269-345-5289 to learn why.","[('Southwest Michigan', 'LOCATION'), ('269-345-5289', 'OTHER')]"
"Design, construction, and installation of high-quality shade solutions.",[]
"Discover handcrafted leather bags, wallets & accessories. Shop online luxury fashion in sustainable leather.",[]
Achieve financial freedom and enjoy superb lifestyle with Alliance In Motion Global Business that is Turning Ordinary People Into Extraordinary Millionaires,"[('Alliance In Motion Global Business', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"When you choose EWASH, the only commitment is our pledge to provide you with superior service and personalised care. No contracts, just quality linens and ...","[('EWASH', 'COMMERCIAL_ITEM')]"
"Oswego, Illinois-based HQC Incorporated is a full-service close-tolerance precision injection-molding company that specializes in high-quality custom-injection and insert-molded products for medical and packaging companies","[('Oswego, Illinois', 'LOCATION'), ('HQC Incorporated', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"It's like Diablo had a lovechild with Dark Souls, a MUD and D&D. Nice little browser rpg game. We even have an android app!","[('Diablo', 'PERSON'), ('Dark Souls', 'TITLE'), ('D&D.', 'TITLE'), ('android', 'TITLE')]"
" 
TeamWave is the best small business CRM, project management & HRMS software. A better way to manage your projects, team and sales.
","[('TeamWave', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"We automate your lead generation system with targeted direct messages.
No paid ads needed. No more cold calls.",[]
"AM Engineering is a multi-disciplined design and engineering company with an established track record, providing proven engineering solutions and support to companies within the Oil and Gas, Iron and Steel, Petrochemical and Energy Industries across the UK & overseas.","[('AM Engineering', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('UK', 'LOCATION')]"
Quantum Homes is a family-run business that specialises in building quality homes on acreages in the picturesque Gisborne and Macedon districts of Victoria.,"[('Quantum Homes', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Gisborne', 'LOCATION'), ('Macedon', 'LOCATION'), ('Victoria', 'LOCATION')]"
"Hire a wide range of mobile variable messaging signs (VMS), solar powered monitoring and visual information systems from MVIS Ltd. Call 01629 580 570.","[('MVIS Ltd.', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('01629 580 570', 'OTHER')]"
"A worldwide provider of premier IT infrastructure solutions. We design and manufacture award-winning products for Pro AV, KVM, cabling, and networking",[]
The owner of this domain has not yet uploaded their website.,[]
"Sundance is passionate about delivering digital marketing solutions and creating digital content to meet today’s needs. Our services have grown from video post-production and 3D walkthrough to include innovative content that is both immersive and interactive. This includes 360 VR presentations with Live Chat, photo-realistic 3D VR animation, interactive projection mapping with motion-sensing technology, and real-time interactive AR presentations. Our extensive list of services will include advanced content using Motion-Capture technology for face, body and fingers; giving life to very realistic real-time, virtual characters, set against any virtual environment imaginable.","[('Sundance', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('both', 'QUANTITY'), ('360', 'QUANTITY')]"
"vesta marine is the leading yachting and technical service in the region. our mission is to provide our clients with the most effective service by combining the right approach, excellent workmanship and quality materials. our professional yacht repair and refit facilities are located on site with the 70,000m2 of hardstand space with a capacity of up to 400t travel lift. ","[('vesta marine', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('70,000m2', 'QUANTITY'), ('up to 400t', 'QUANTITY')]"
"An online events platform featuring free, paid, and fundraising events. Share your expertise with the world, or enjoy new experiences from the comfort of wherever you are",[]
Platinum PR is based in Melbourne and is a vibrant lifestyle agency with a reputation for developing ground-breaking campaigns.,"[('Platinum PR', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Melbourne', 'LOCATION')]"
"Valencia News - English International news from Valencia, Spain","[('Valencia News', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('English', 'OTHER'), ('Valencia, Spain', 'LOCATION')]"
Creative Advisors for Your Bright Ideas,[]
Reliable and consistent Forex signals by professional traders at your fingertips. Access a growing community of profitable traders and take your trading to the next level.,[]
"C2 Enterprise is a software provider specialized in offering complete IT Service Management, service desk and helpdesk business solutions, based on ITIL®. C2 ATOM software is made to improve IT support and service centers teams efficiency.","[('C2 Enterprise', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('ITIL®', 'TITLE'), ('C2 ATOM', 'TITLE')]"
Lamont is the solution to your Supplier Selection - Finance - CRM - Payroll & HR - Cloud Solutions - IT Project Management and so much more.,"[('Lamont', 'TITLE')]"
"New Media Consulting provides complete multimedia consulting, development and marketing services.","[('New Media Consulting', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Best Orca whale watching in the San Juan Islands and Puget Sound off the coast of Washington State, near Seattle. Guaranteed to see a whale on all tours!","[('San Juan Islands', 'LOCATION'), ('Puget Sound', 'LOCATION'), ('Washington State', 'LOCATION'), ('Seattle', 'LOCATION')]"
Blupool is a swimming pool construction and maintenance company in Durban North with over 21 years experience. Excellent workmanship and service,"[('Blupool', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Durban North', 'LOCATION'), ('over 21 years', 'QUANTITY')]"
"It's time for men to take control of their faces. Lumin simplifies the daily routines for guys to combat dark eye circles, acne scarring, dry skin, lines and wrinkles, clogged pores caused by oily skin, and more. Invest in your face the way you do in other aspects of life, and EARN your best look ever.",[]
Financial Advisors Lmited,[]
"ProHealth Marketing Pte. Ltd. - Everything for good health
63 Jalan Pemimpin, #04-05 Pemimpin Industrial Building,
Singapore 577219","[('ProHealth Marketing Pte. Ltd.', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('63 Jalan Pemimpin,', 'LOCATION'), ('#04-05', 'OTHER'), ('Pemimpin Industrial Building,\nSingapore 577219', 'LOCATION')]"
"Care One has been a proven leader in staffing solutions for the past 24 years delivering short-term, long-term, and per diem professionals.","[('Care One', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('24 years', 'QUANTITY')]"
Skills Kemahiran Kolej Yayasan Pahang Advanced Skills Computer System Bakery Kitchen Practise Electrical Automotive Fashion Welding Office Management VTO Short Courses,"[('Kolej Yayasan Pahang', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"CS Motorsports is your 1-Stop-Shop for all things automotive! Wheels, Tires, Lift Kits, Remote Start, Leather/Heated Seats, Window Tint and more! WE FINANCE!","[('CS Motorsports', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('1-Stop-Shop', 'QUANTITY')]"
This is a default index page for a new domain.,[]
"Find out which are the most amazing photos, videos and stories around the web.",[]
"Official site for UK rock band AT THE SUN. Keep up to date with news, reviews and tour dates | New album 'Leave Before The Light' Out Now","[('UK', 'LOCATION'), ('AT THE SUN', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Leave Before The Light', 'TITLE')]"
"Rivi is an AI that you can have a conversation with to plan a fully personalized trip - Flights, Hotels, Vacation Rentals, Things to do, Restaurants and Nightlife.","[('Rivi', 'OTHER'), ('AI', 'OTHER')]"
"We've been providing proven IT services to businesses since 1973. It's our mission to deliver the right mix of secure and reliable hardware, software and services to support your business. Consider us your always there and always care tech team.","[('1973', 'DATE')]"
"Whether you run a restaurant, concession stand, or packed school cafeteria, Atlantic Distributors has all the right equipment and supplies for your busy establishment.","[('Atlantic Distributors', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"This website is for sale! jatropha.com is your first and best source for all of the information you’re looking for. From general topics to more of what you would expect to find here, jatropha.com has it all. We hope you find what you are searching for!","[('jatropha.com', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('first', 'QUANTITY'), ('jatropha.com', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Web site created using create-react-app,[]
"Choose MBicycle, a professional software outsourcing company, to get your custom web and mobile solutions!","[('MBicycle', 'TITLE')]"
Aircraft Shopper Online is the most comprehensive and up-to-date aircraft listing source. More than half the aircraft dealers and brokers in North America use ASO to publicize their available inventory.,"[('More than half the aircraft', 'QUANTITY'), ('North America', 'LOCATION'), ('ASO', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"We aim to provide the harbour towage, terminal management and logistic services, through our involved, dedicated and skilled people, delivering excellent customer service.",[]
"Sidewalk Cafe in Denton Texas. Serving Breakfast all day, brunch, lunch, and dinner. Meeting/Event space for Denton","[('Sidewalk Cafe', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Denton Texas', 'LOCATION'), ('Denton', 'LOCATION')]"
"Home Inspections By Eric is a service of M & ME Properties LLC, serving communities of Western North Carolina.","[('Eric', 'PERSON'), ('M & ME Properties LLC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Western North Carolina', 'LOCATION')]"
We are a boutique Accounting Firm based in Perth. Our team has extensive experience in accounting and taxation advice through to holistic business consulting.,"[('Perth', 'LOCATION')]"
"Turn your business and your profession into a Human Experience Agency, and become the Human Experience Trusted Advisor, through Smart Income Methods",[]
"Here  you will get English Grammar, Language skills, General Knowledge, education, scholarship news, and  reading, writing and speaking skills","[('English', 'OTHER')]"
"King & Partners is an agency providing strategy, branding,creative, campaigns, marketing and eCommerce servicesto exceptional brands across an array of categories.","[('King & Partners', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Thames Enrich is a training provider mainly provides personal digital marketing training to the SME in Malaysia. Our mission is to provide an entrepreneur solutions.,"[('Thames Enrich', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Malaysia', 'LOCATION')]"
"Duraco Specialty Tapes is a manufacturer and distributor of adhesive tapes, foam tapes, hook and loop tapes, removable tapes, and other adhesive products for a wide array of applications.","[('Duraco Specialty Tapes', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Just another WordPress site,"[('WordPress', 'TITLE')]"
"The Dockside Group manages some of the best venues and restaurants in Sydney. Choose from L’Aqua and Dockside, located at Cockle Bay Wharf, Star Room and Eat Love Pizza overlooking  Darling Harbour or Waterfront, Wolfies, or the Italian Village, all located on the sandstone shores of The Rocks overlooking the Sydney Opera House.  Each with a unique ambience and provides a stunning backdrop combined with Dockside’s exquisite menu and superior service, your next event will be a day to remember.","[('Dockside Group', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Sydney', 'LOCATION'), ('L’Aqua', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Dockside', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Cockle Bay Wharf', 'LOCATION'), ('Star', 'LOCATION'), ('Room', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Eat Love Pizza', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Darling Harbour', 'LOCATION'), ('Waterfront', 'LOCATION'), ('Wolfies', 'LOCATION'), ('Italian Village', 'LOCATION'), ('The Rocks', 'LOCATION'), ('Sydney Opera House', 'LOCATION'), ('Each', 'QUANTITY'), ('Dockside', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Dycor creates complete Process Control,Data Acquisition, and Logging solutions for Industrial manufacturing, Oil and Gas and Municipal services.","[('Dycor', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"GSM Marketing provides a complete menu of marketing services for wealth managers, financial advisors and retirement plan professionals.","[('GSM Marketing', 'TITLE')]"
Stand out with our premium clothing concepts this season.,[]
Nautical Bits UK - Shop the Ultimate Nautical T-Shirt Collection For Sailors. ALL of our designs are created based on a Sailing or Boating theme...,"[('UK', 'LOCATION')]"
NJ Technologies offers businesses the opportunity to leverage from the strong domain & technical expertise of a richly experienced & committed team. Know more!,"[('NJ Technologies', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Responsive HTML5 Template,"[('HTML5', 'OTHER')]"
"Sideways is a digital-first branding and creative agency. Our hospitality 
and lifestyle expertise deeply influences our ability to differentiate your 
brand.",[]
"Manufacturer of Quality Pet Products in Ontario, CA since 2003 including Automatic Pet Feeders, Cat Trees, Dog Kennels / Cages, Pet Water Fountains & more!","[('Ontario, CA', 'LOCATION'), ('2003', 'DATE')]"
Overseas Education Consultants in Pune - Qbix Academia is the best overseas education consultant in Pune for all the global higher education. We are the leaders in the educational consultancy and consult the students for study abroad. ,"[('Pune', 'LOCATION'), ('Qbix Academia', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Pune', 'LOCATION')]"
A world-leading integrated project and programme management consultancy.,[]
"The world's first pet toy that allows you to play with your pet dog or cat from anywhere, anytime.<br>","[('first pet toy', 'QUANTITY')]"
"maxdiamond, 3D generalist and motion graphics designer based in Bangalore, India.","[('maxdiamond', 'PERSON'), ('Bangalore, India', 'LOCATION')]"
"If your facility has power quality issues and your electrical system is experiencing issues and unnecessary maintenance, then O&M Resources is here to help you with products and technology dedicated to filtering, protecting and backing up your electrical system. Technology that keeps your electrical system running effectively and efficiently.","[('O&M Resources', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Expert Engineers are a fast growing professionally managed engineering comapny engaged in the manufacturing of Electrical Control Panels, swichboard, List of top suppliers of Distribution Control Panel suppliers, manufacturers, wholesalers, traders with Electric Control Panel prices for buying.",[]
Goldray are the new psych rock project from ex-REEF guitarist Kenwyn House!,"[('Goldray', 'PERSON'), ('REEF', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Kenwyn House', 'PERSON')]"
AV Integration is a proudly South Australian owned & operated company.,"[('AV Integration', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('South Australian', 'OTHER')]"
A leading provider of digital and retail international money transfer and payments services and foreign currency exchange services.,[]
"Rides, Food & Games for your next event.",[]
The Best Provably Fair Bitcoin Dice Site with REAL Instant Withdrawals. No Registration Required. Join our Contests with a Huge Prizes! This is Your Chance to Win Big with Luckygames!,"[('Luckygames', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"At OPPLE, We’re not just building better lighting, were inventing better light. Get to know our company and products today.","[('OPPLE', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('today', 'DATE')]"
"ABM Enterprise a holding company for Design , Entertainment and Motorsport","[('ABM Enterprise', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Slash your energy bills with sustainable & reliable solar power. Beyond Solar is a locally owned company providing solar panels for Sydney and NSW homes.,"[('Beyond Solar', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Sydney', 'LOCATION'), ('NSW', 'LOCATION')]"
"Test equipment for sale and rental. Excalibur Engineering offers calibration services & repair of most electrical, instrument & pressure test equipment.","[('Excalibur Engineering', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Tools for making the internet fast, accessible, expressive, and green.",[]
"Auger Filler Pouch Packing Machine, Automatic Filling and Sealing Machines for Food Industry & Semi Automatic filling Machines Exporter offered by Genius Engineering from Faridabad, Haryana, India","[('Auger Filler', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Genius Engineering', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Faridabad, Haryana, India', 'LOCATION')]"
"Dillard's: Shop designer dresses, shoes, clothing, handbags, cosmetics and beauty, bedding, lingerie, wedding registry items and more.","[(""Dillard's"", 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"An award-winning general contractor and construction management team, ACL Construction (s) Pte Ltd has been building structures of enduring quality for more than 10 years.

We have constructed in virtually every industry and have broad experience with Housing & Development Board & Lift Upgrading Programmes, Land & Transport Authority Road & Rail Works, Chemical & Water Reclamation Plant Projects, Singapore Air Force Camps / Prisons / Naval Bases and Ministry of Education School Buildings / Upgrading works.

ACL Construction (s) Pte Ltd is a primary contractor working in both the public and private sectors with contracts ranging from fixed-price, cost-plus, design-build-operate, to fast-track construction projects.","[('ACL Construction (s) Pte Ltd', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('more than 10 years', 'QUANTITY'), ('Board', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Singapore Air Force Camps', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('ACL Construction (s) Pte Ltd', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('both', 'QUANTITY')]"
Solaris Resources is a multi-asset copper company focused on exploring and developing copper projects in the Americas.,"[('Solaris Resources', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Americas', 'LOCATION')]"
"It is very difficult to manufacture high quality wooden door in Bangladesh, due to the fact that, our weather don't produce high quality timber, we get some best quality timber.","[('Bangladesh', 'LOCATION')]"
"The Rose Bower florist is situated in the Nottinghamshire town of Sutton-in-Ashfield, whether it’s a birthday, anniversary, sympathy or celebration, we use a selection of the finest, freshest cut flowers and foliages to create your design and  are able to offer same day delivery up until 2pm.","[('Rose Bower', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Nottinghamshire', 'LOCATION'), ('Sutton-in-Ashfield', 'LOCATION'), ('2pm', 'DATE')]"
This domain may be for sale,[]
"Personal blog of XuanYan, in which he writes about web development and some other things.","[('XuanYan', 'PERSON')]"
Welcome to North Terminal. IT support services for homes and businesses in Northumberland and W3C compliant web design for the world!,"[('North Terminal', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Northumberland', 'LOCATION')]"
STX Precision (JB) Sdn. Bhd. is a Malaysia based manufacturer of precision metal parts and components using high-pressure die-casting of aluminium and zinc alloys.,"[('STX Precision (JB) Sdn. Bhd.', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Malaysia', 'LOCATION')]"
"Dasse, combining delicate esthetics of quality with the power of corporate solidity, is a brand originated in Turkey with a global combined network. The firm dynamically conducts business operations in Europe, Asia and several countries in the Middle East.","[('Turkey', 'LOCATION'), ('Europe', 'LOCATION'), ('Asia', 'LOCATION'), ('several countries', 'QUANTITY'), ('Middle East', 'LOCATION')]"
"Silver Star Properties | Top REALTORS® and market leaders on Silver Star Mountain Resort, Priscilla and Don are your dedicated and successful team!","[('Silver Star Properties', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Silver Star Mountain Resort', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Priscilla', 'PERSON'), ('Don', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Harvest Klang is a great local church located in the Klang Valley. We have vibrant and effective ministries ranging from toddlers, kids, teens, working adults to senior adults. If you are from Klang or you’re new in town, we’d love to get to know you better. ","[('Harvest Klang', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Klang Valley', 'LOCATION'), ('Klang', 'LOCATION')]"
Vital Nutrients is a leading manufacturer of high quality nutritional supplements trusted by healthcare practitioners and hospitals worldwide. Learn more here!,"[('Vital Nutrients', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Tossing Pancakes in a Force Seven!,"[('Seven', 'QUANTITY')]"
"Extreme Cleaning Services provides various outdoor cleaning services in Ogden, UT, and surrounding areas. Inquire about our window washing & deep clean service!","[('Extreme Cleaning Services', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Ogden, UT', 'LOCATION')]"
V.eye - Keep your business on,[]
"Boston website design and web design, Boston, MA - We create custom websites and offer hosting services. Maximize your web presence. Call 617 924-0077","[('Boston', 'LOCATION'), ('Boston, MA', 'LOCATION'), ('617 924-0077', 'OTHER')]"
Quality stair parts for contractors,[]
We're a product design company with nearly 60 years of success creating some of the world's most well-known products.,"[('nearly 60 years', 'QUANTITY')]"
"Grand Living offers a collection of elegant French Provincial, contemporary & children's furniture that will accentuate your home and provide your family with years of luxury living.","[('Grand Living', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('French', 'OTHER')]"
"Laxton Properties is a small, independent property development company run by Chartered Surveyors and focused on the delivery of high quality, well built homes in great locations throughout Hertfordshire and Buckinghamshire.","[('Laxton Properties', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Chartered Surveyors', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hertfordshire', 'LOCATION'), ('Buckinghamshire', 'LOCATION')]"
BKP is a niche developer that develops unique projects. Our projects ,"[('BKP', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Excellent Health Starts with You. At NBI we formulate and manufacture products that give you results. NBI was founded in 2006 and we’re proud to be making..,"[('NBI', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('NBI', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('2006', 'DATE')]"
Just another WordPress site,"[('WordPress', 'TITLE')]"
"Passionate about Payroll, the ESOS team has over 250 years of Payroll experience","[('Payroll', 'TITLE'), ('ESOS', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('over 250 years', 'QUANTITY')]"
" H2 Design is a full service interior design firm. We create interiors, 
kitchens, bathrooms and additions. We manage the process from start to 
finish. H2 Design brings clients quality design for a fraction of the cost 
of a high priced design firms.","[('H2 Design', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('H2 Design', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"CN Cleaning provides residential common part area cleaning service on a regular basis. If it is a residential or commercial building and you need a reliable, efficient cleaning service we have you covered.","[('CN Cleaning', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Fast Star can you bring your ideas to life or suggest strategies and ideas you may have never thought of before.,"[('Fast', 'OTHER'), ('Star', 'TITLE')]"
Polaris Scientific is a premier company providing laboratory equipment solution in Kenya and East African region,"[('Polaris Scientific', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Kenya', 'LOCATION'), ('East African', 'LOCATION')]"
Pronounced as Carbon. We are a skincare brand rooted in wellness. Discover and shop our luxurious range of bath and body products powered by nature. Free shipping available within India.,"[('Carbon', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('India', 'LOCATION')]"
Mercutek: Adding value to secondary Raw Materials.,"[('Mercutek', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Conroy’s desire is to serve our clientele with top technology consultants and services, leading to extended contracts and long-lasting successful relationships.","[('Conroy', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Ibramarketing is a Full-Service Marketing Agency that specializes in Google Adwords, Social Media Marketing, and Web designs. Call today for a FREE consultation. We are here to help.","[('Ibramarketing', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Google Adwords', 'TITLE'), ('today', 'DATE')]"
TOP US is a specialist recruiting firm that works with Japanese-related businesses throughout the US.,"[('TOP US', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Japanese', 'OTHER'), ('US', 'LOCATION')]"
"Since 1979, Manning Company specializes in hand crafted finest custom made luxurious tailored bespoke suits, trousers shirts and tuxedos","[('1979', 'DATE'), ('Manning Company', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
SG Logistics is a delivery platform where you can sign up for opportunities to deliver healthy salads and bowls from Sweetgreen to local businesses that have signed up for Sweetgreen’s Outpost program.,"[('SG Logistics', 'TITLE'), ('Sweetgreen', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Sweetgreen', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Outpost', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"With the lean approach and building software, optimise your construction schedule, boost productivity and maximise customer satisfaction.",[]
"Ground Engineering (GE) magazine provides information on new and practical aspects of geotechnics, engineering geology and geo-environmental engineering.","[('Ground Engineering', 'TITLE'), ('GE', 'TITLE')]"
"TBC Provide professional marketing solutions for a wide range of businesses. Our services include marketing, advertising...","[('TBC', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"We are a clothing brand that offers t-shirts, hoodies, shorts and mask. We want to unite people from all walks of like and all over the world, to come together as one.",[]
"SolidBox was founded by SolidWorks Users for SolidWorks Users. Our mission is very simple: Provide Proven Hardware that can Handle the Demands of SolidWorks. Whether you’re a new user, or a seasoned Simulation guru, you came to right place to learn what it takes to run SolidWorks Better, Faster, and more Reliable. SolidBox is a turnkey hardware integrator for SolidWorks end users. We sell servers, desktops, and laptops that are configured specifically for SolidWorks. Our systems arrive with SolidWorks client and/or server software pre-installed. Take a look at our Creative, Engineer, and Professional series products to learn more. SolidBox does not sell SolidWorks software, rather we work with your SolidWorks Value Added Reseller (VAR) to make sure your license of SolidWorks, SolidWorks Simulation, Workgroup PDM, & Enterprise PDM is properly installed and ready to work for you. At SolidBox we take a no B.S. approach to configuring our systems for a variety of users. We have no direct association with Dassault Systemes SolidWorks Corporation, so we pledge to give you the straight scoop on stability and reliability. Our founder was given the Elite Applications Engineer award by Dassault Systemes SolidWorks Corporation in 2008, and has been a SolidWorks user since 1997. He started SolidBox after years of helping frustrated customers overcome their hardware related issues. Read more about SolidBox.Take a look around our site, and keep coming back. We are dedicated to make SolidBox the premiere hardware resource for all SolidWorks users. Coming soon, we will have Industry and Customer specific “Ground Breaker” segments that spotlight SolidBox customers and shows how they make the most out of SolidWorks and SolidBox hardware.","[('SolidBox', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('SolidWorks', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('SolidWorks', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('SolidWorks', 'TITLE'), ('SolidWorks', 'TITLE'), ('SolidBox', 'TITLE'), ('SolidWorks', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('SolidWorks', 'TITLE'), ('SolidWorks', 'TITLE'), ('SolidBox', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('SolidWorks', 'TITLE'), ('SolidWorks', 'TITLE'), ('SolidWorks', 'TITLE'), ('SolidWorks', 'TITLE'), ('Workgroup', 'TITLE'), ('SolidBox', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Dassault Systemes SolidWorks Corporation', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Elite Applications Engineer', 'TITLE'), ('Dassault Systemes SolidWorks Corporation', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('2008', 'DATE'), ('SolidWorks', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('1997', 'DATE'), ('SolidBox', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('SolidBox.Take', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('SolidBox', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('SolidWorks', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('SolidBox', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('SolidWorks', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('SolidBox', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Production Engineering Corporation provides a range of contract manufacturing services, including sheet metal fabrication, CNC machining & more.","[('Production Engineering Corporation', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Call Center Professional Services, Telecommunications Implementation Services, Telecommunications Dispatch Services, Staff Augmentation",[]
"Lewis Deep Democracy teaches tools to resolve conflict by gaining the wisdom of all sides, instead of avoiding tension and conflict.","[('Lewis', 'PERSON'), ('Deep Democracy', 'TITLE'), ('all sides', 'QUANTITY')]"
"We help you to develop and commercialise your innovations based on the Licensing business model. Our values : Collaboration, transparency, openness to the world",[]
Vetted IT Support for financial and professional service firms in Tulsa and Oklahoma City.,"[('Tulsa', 'LOCATION'), ('Oklahoma City', 'LOCATION')]"
" Red Cloud Services provides human factors and other engineering services. 
We are a native american owned small disadvantaged business in Washington 
DC.","[('Red Cloud Services', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('american', 'LOCATION'), ('Washington \r\nDC', 'LOCATION')]"
"Equilibrium Body Shapers and Jeans, manufactures and distributes Shapewear Made in Colombia, including Post Op & Every day Girdles, Postpartum, waist trainers, shapers & cinchers. Women jeans designed for you to look amazing. Plus Size up to 7X and 22. Jeans Colombianos & Fajas Colombianas. FREE SHIPPING. Find out more","[('Equilibrium', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Colombia', 'LOCATION'), ('up to 7X', 'QUANTITY'), ('22', 'QUANTITY'), ('Colombianos', 'OTHER'), ('Colombianas', 'OTHER')]"
"The leading resource for XRF lead based paint detection equipment, discussion of lead based paint issues, listings of resources that provide information on how to protect your children from lead poisoning, lead based paint news and articles, a complete discussion of Title X, Lead Paint disclosure, Lead Paint Liability issues for involved parties such as Realtors, Sellers, Buyers, Landlords and tenants, a description of XRF testing for lead based paint","[('XRF', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Title X', 'OTHER'), ('XRF', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Located in the heart of Georgetown, Penang, Prangin Mall enjoys direct connectivity with all over Penang as the main Bus Stop is located in the mall.","[('Georgetown', 'LOCATION'), ('Penang', 'LOCATION'), ('Prangin Mall', 'LOCATION'), ('Penang', 'LOCATION')]"
"T & G Electrical is a licensed electrical contractor providing commericial & residential electrical service in Dedham, Westwood, Brookline, Chestnut Hill, Newton, & Needham MA","[('T & G Electrical', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Dedham', 'LOCATION'), ('Westwood', 'LOCATION'), ('Brookline', 'LOCATION'), ('Chestnut Hill', 'LOCATION'), ('Newton', 'LOCATION'), ('Needham MA', 'LOCATION')]"
Ohio Athletic Conference (OAC),"[('Ohio Athletic Conference', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('OAC', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Investing in innovative, early-stage, deep-tech companies fight climate change and accelerate the zero carbon transition.","[('zero carbon', 'QUANTITY')]"
"We're Christchurch builders, building and renovating homes throughout Canterbury. We make your technical renovation look easy. Call now to transform your home!","[('Christchurch', 'LOCATION'), ('Canterbury', 'LOCATION')]"
Welcome to the world of CHOPARD -  Find sparkling and exclusive Swiss watches and jewellery on the official Chopard website.,"[('CHOPARD -', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Swiss', 'OTHER'), ('Chopard', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Our store focuses on positive message t shirts and mugs to start your day on a positive note. We have shirts such as positive shirts, stay positive shirts, body positive shirts, funny quote shirts, cute quote shirts, inspirational quote shirts, workout quote shirts also We have funny coffee mugs, customized mugs.",[]
"Get online with Website Builder! Create a free 2-page website to go with your new domain. Start now for free, no credit card required!","[('2-page', 'QUANTITY')]"
"Synaptica Taxonomy and Ontology Software for Knowledge Organization Systems (KOS), Linked Data, Knowledge Graphs, RDF, and Auto Classification","[('Synaptica', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Knowledge Organization', 'OTHER')]"
"SH Integrated Services is a L6 full-fledged building contractor and licensed builder specialized in integrated building services that covers maintenance of M&E systems, water supply and sanitary systems, building works and lightning protection systems. It has consistently delivered on-time and on-budget – prominent projects.","[('SH Integrated Services', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('M&E', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Cool Shades- Window Tinting in St. Charles. Automotive, Residential and Commercial","[('St. Charles', 'LOCATION')]"
"A Cincinnati distributer & assembler of Gates, Kuriyama, Titan, Parker industrial hose coupled with banded, swaged, crimped, internally expanded fittings made by Pride Cast Metals, PT Coupling Company, Parker, Dayco, & Dixon Fittings.","[('Cincinnati', 'LOCATION'), ('Gates', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Kuriyama', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Titan', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Parker', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Pride Cast Metals', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('PT Coupling Company', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Parker', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Dayco', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Dixon Fittings', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"At KOYAH we are all about helping others (and ourselves) eat more whole fruits and veggies. We exist to inspire health through simple, whole-food products.","[('KOYAH', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Discover the most exclusive Properties on the beaches of Valencia and Alicante. Visit our portfolio of properties on the Coast.,"[('Valencia', 'LOCATION'), ('Alicante', 'LOCATION')]"
"Travel Guide A to Z | weather, photos, informations",[]
"Sanger Australia provides tailored Beef, Lamb, Goat and Chicken supply programs to over 40 countries across Retail Ready, Food Service and Commodity products.","[('Sanger Australia', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('over 40 countries', 'QUANTITY')]"
Check out this GoDaddy hosted webpage! http://qualityfrontier.com.,"[('GoDaddy', 'TITLE'), ('http://qualityfrontier.com', 'OTHER')]"
"Umami Collective is a distributed team of all-senior consultants and developers. We have delivered projects for large agencies, world class retail brands and industry leaders. We work with open web and mobile technologies.
","[('Umami Collective', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Based in Brighton, Sussex we offer secured loans against luxury assets such 
as cars, number plates, luxury watches, fine jewellery and art. No Credit 
Checks. Fast decisions. Professional and Discreet High End Pawnbrokers. 
Personal and business lending. 01273 950900","[('Brighton, Sussex', 'LOCATION'), ('01273 950900', 'OTHER')]"
"NICEIC & ECA Approved Energy Efficient Advisors & Commercial Electrical Contractors covering Kent, Surrey, Sussex & London. SSIP Compliant","[('NICEIC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('ECA', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Kent', 'LOCATION'), ('Surrey', 'LOCATION'), ('Sussex', 'LOCATION'), ('London', 'LOCATION')]"
"Greyer is a cannabis consulting firm dedicated to helping clients navigate the regulations, ethics and compliance requirements of operating a cannabis operation, specifically those in the infused edibles space.","[('Greyer', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Liquid Suspension, Unlike Chemotherapy and other cancer Treatments, Body Revival works on the line of Immunotherapy and Boosts your body system naturally to fight Cancer.",[]
20 years of experience Coffee Machine Warehouse is your one stop coffee machine specialist shop! We stock a wide range of over 1000 commercial and domestic automatic & more coffee machines in our Melbourne. Click to here to see our full range.,"[('20 years', 'QUANTITY'), ('one stop', 'QUANTITY'), ('over 1000 commercial', 'QUANTITY'), ('automatic', 'QUANTITY'), ('Melbourne', 'LOCATION')]"
"At Westminster Consulting, we specialize in providing incomparable fiduciary advice and counsel coupled with thoughtful investment research to our clients.","[('Westminster Consulting', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Leading Whole House Fan experts in San Diego County. Call Our Whole House Fan San Diego Office today! Modern, efficient Whole House Fans to cool your home.","[('San Diego County', 'LOCATION'), ('San', 'LOCATION'), ('Diego Office', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('today', 'DATE')]"
"I am a freelance web developer based in Hornchurch, East London. I specialise in front end and .NET-based CMS (Content Management System) development.","[('Hornchurch, East London', 'LOCATION')]"
Malaysia's Premiere Badminton Club participating in the Malaysia Purple League. Home of Badminton legend Lee Chong Wei.,"[('Malaysia', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Premiere Badminton Club', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Malaysia Purple League', 'EVENT'), ('Lee Chong Wei', 'PERSON')]"
"This website is for sale! ipeak.us is your first and best source for all of the information you’re looking for. From general topics to more of what you would expect to find here, ipeak.us has it all. We hope you find what you are searching for!","[('ipeak.us', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('first', 'QUANTITY'), ('ipeak.us', 'TITLE')]"
One of the leading design firms in India,"[('One', 'QUANTITY'), ('the leading', 'QUANTITY'), ('firms', 'QUANTITY'), ('India', 'LOCATION')]"
Looking to become a Foster Parent or adopt a child? Outpatient Services | Youth Services | Case Management | Medication Management - Empowering lives,[]
"Events, Strategy and Creative, Design and Production",[]
"Applechem is a functional cosmetic ingredient supplier with a diverse range of products for cosmetics, personal care, suncare, hair care and  homecare formulations.","[('Applechem', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Juicy Media is a leading UK specialist web development company, based in MediaCityUK, Manchester and Farringdon, London. Tried and trusted. From start ups and SME’s, to fortune 500 enterprises, over the years we have worked with some of the UK’s largest brands.","[('Juicy Media', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('UK', 'LOCATION'), ('MediaCityUK', 'LOCATION'), ('Manchester', 'LOCATION'), ('Farringdon, London', 'LOCATION'), ('fortune 500 enterprises', 'QUANTITY'), ('UK', 'LOCATION')]"
Handcrafted soaps and skincare with a touch of luxury,[]
"Join the Livingston community in North Calgary (NW and NE) embracing healthy living within a small-town atmosphere, defined by warm hospitality and a vibrant residential association.","[('Livingston', 'LOCATION'), ('North Calgary', 'LOCATION'), ('NW', 'LOCATION'), ('NE', 'LOCATION')]"
"Kamico Ltd, From Design to Delivery. UK based importer of Underwear, nightwear, socks, support and solutionwear. Outerwear, including sports and activewear","[('Kamico Ltd', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('UK', 'LOCATION')]"
"Technique Solutions is the Melbourne Metro area's first choice for Site, Civil and Safety Supplies.","[('Technique Solutions', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Melbourne Metro', 'LOCATION'), ('first choice', 'QUANTITY')]"
"Concrete Science is the leading decorative and traditional concrete contractor in the Twin Cities of Minnesota and committed to quality, service, and value.","[('Science', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Twin Cities of Minnesota', 'LOCATION')]"
The Adhesive Specialist,[]
"GSpeed specializes in high performance road race corvette, Camaro, mustang, and exotic sports cars. Engineered solutions for high performance street, track or racing we have the answers.","[('GSpeed', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Camaro', 'COMMERCIAL_ITEM'), ('mustang', 'COMMERCIAL_ITEM')]"
"Faux Wood Beams, Tongue & Groove, Corbels & Columns | All designed and manufactured in the USA | Delivered directly to your home!","[('USA', 'LOCATION')]"
"We offer any kind of service for electronic systems in use for Pharmacovigilance and Clinical research activities.
Our value proposition is the ability of designing our services based on client profile, organization, budget and needs, keeping Quality always at the center.",[]
"Visible Power offer total energy solutions for commercial and industrial companies in Indiana. We help clients take control of their energy usage and discover cost-saving opportunities. We provide our customers with effective energy efficiency products, including the world's most all-inclusive energy management system - Eniscope.","[('Visible Power', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Indiana', 'LOCATION')]"
Take the of the anxiety out of investing by letting us do the work for you.,[]
"Zero Degrees is an Asian-Hispanic inspired chain that specializes in signature smoothies, coffee & tea, hot snacks and more!","[('Zero Degrees', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Asian', 'OTHER'), ('Hispanic', 'OTHER')]"
Range of Handmade Wooden Driveway Gates. Made From Redwood and Manufactured To Almost Any Height Or Width. Free UK Delivery*,"[('UK', 'LOCATION')]"
"Icon Digital is a Digital Agency specialising in Web Design Sydney wide, also focusing on eCommerce, Business Grade Hosting and more.","[('Icon Digital', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Sydney', 'LOCATION')]"
"Laboratory Equipment, Laboratory Glassware, scientific labware ",[]
"RBTC is proud to be the main provider of Rosemary Beach’s logo apparel and gear, as well as offer a fun eclectic mix of designer home décor items & gifts.","[('RBTC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Rosemary Beach', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Embedded Product Development, Product Design, Product Testing, Product Engineering Services, IoT System Integration",[]
BioMedServ offers a suite of life science services to help biological and medical device companies execute product and marketing strategies.,"[('BioMedServ', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
--- Recent Blogs --- Read More --- Popular Blogs --- Read More,[]
"Atozeta Mediscience AsiaPac (M) Sdn. Bhd. provides expertise in the areas of medico-marketing promotional inputs, scientific writing solutions, and patient education.","[('Atozeta Mediscience AsiaPac (M) Sdn. Bhd.', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Grindstone Creative is a leading integrated creative communications agency, based in Geelong, Australia. Specialists in brand strategy, digital, creative and content.","[('Grindstone Creative', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Geelong, Australia', 'LOCATION')]"
Read through our story and feel all our motorcycle passion. ,[]
"Queens Collection is a brand for the empowered, dominant and tenacious woman. Sound like you? Come see us!","[('Queens Collection', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Created specifically to address the demand for environmentally conscious solutions, our emissions free, silent, generators deliver safe, reliable power to movie and television productions of all size and genre.","[('all size and genre', 'QUANTITY')]"
"Skyreal is an industrial VR software solutions provider. Our software is made with love in Paris, France, where it's used by industries like Airbus, Ariane Espace...","[('Skyreal', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Paris, France', 'LOCATION'), ('Airbus', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Ariane Espace', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
New Faces Models & Talent Casting,[]
"Car Park Management and Consultancy
",[]
This domain may be for sale!,[]
"TBX is a website design and development agency based in Grand Rapids, Michigan that specializes in brand-centric digital marketing.","[('TBX', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Grand Rapids, Michigan', 'LOCATION')]"
"iLogic Solutions provides web development and hosting services to Springfield, Missouri utilizing the latest technologies in web design.","[('iLogic Solutions', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Springfield, Missouri', 'LOCATION')]"
"A-Gas offers everything you need to know about Refrigerants, Industrial Gases, Halon, Chemicals as well as technical advice. Responsible and Sustainable. A-Gas Together We Can!","[('A-Gas', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Cookies N Crème Ice Cream Shop in Denver NC offers a large selection of delicious Ice Cream Treats, Snow Cones, Italian Ice,  Desserts, Homemade Churros.","[('Cookies N Crème', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Denver NC', 'LOCATION')]"
"Try SkyMark's software. It helps you do your best work. Get the management, planning and thinking tools that teams use most for innovation, process improvement, quality, and problem solving.","[('SkyMark', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Washington DC Parking is a pain. From parking tickets, to rules, to rates, it's a real headache. DCParking.org is here to help you avoid the pain.","[('Washington DC', 'LOCATION'), ('DCParking.org', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Financial Market Association of Singapore,"[('Financial Market Association of Singapore', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Complete building service to bring your commercial or domestic building project from concept to completion - members of Federation of Master Builders.,"[('Federation of Master Builders', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Shop powered by PrestaShop,"[('PrestaShop', 'TITLE')]"
Welcome to our website.,[]
"Web Squared Ltd is a small company, based in on the boundary of Berkshire, Wiltshire and Hampshire, which specialises in helping other small businesses get","[('Web Squared Ltd', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Berkshire', 'LOCATION'), ('Wiltshire', 'LOCATION'), ('Hampshire', 'LOCATION')]"
"Shape the future: At MAGURA, we develop innovative products for bikes and motorcycles.","[('MAGURA', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"AdTech Metallurgical Materials Co., Ltd is an international enterprise. It mainly supplies new materials for the aluminum alloy foundry industry. AdTech focuses on the research and development of onli","[('AdTech Metallurgical Materials Co., Ltd', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('AdTech', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Real-time gps fleet and asset tracking, speeding, routing, dispatching, idling, driving behavior and much more. Used by over 15,000 businesses.","[('over 15,000 businesses', 'QUANTITY')]"
"Here at CS&L Properties, we are a Property Management Company that has mulitple Vacation rentals and Houses for rent. We also buy and sell homes. ","[('CS&L Properties', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"OTC Construction specializing in decorative concrete. Sidewalks/Pads/Patios | Curbs | Bollards and More
","[('OTC Construction', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
European Baromedical Association (EBAss) is an international non profit Association. EBAss has purpose to encourage Hyperbaric personnel to a safe approach in daily practices.,"[('European Baromedical Association', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('EBAss', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('EBAss', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hyperbaric', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
All pure wool Cashmere/merino Boiled Wool Possum Fur,[]
"Make your life easier as an event planner! Don't waste time on registration and name tags. Our apps do it all for you, including badge printing on the spot.",[]
"Intermech provides construction management, design assist, and HVAC services","[('Intermech', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"QCEG MEDIA is creative group of people specialising in digital & print publication, advertising, public relations and live events management. ","[('QCEG MEDIA', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Here to liven up your cup and show you that instant coffee doesn’t need to be boring. No added sugar & no nasties. Just smooth, quick, delicious coffee️.",[]
A diversified national asset management firm providing investment capital to small businesses that are underserved by traditional sources of financing.,[]
"Order flowers online from your florist in Richmond Hill, ON. FlowerSmart, offers fresh flowers and hand delivery right to your door in Richmond Hill.","[('Richmond Hill, ON', 'LOCATION'), ('FlowerSmart', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Richmond Hill', 'LOCATION')]"
Croakun turns your Analytics & Intelligence ideas into successful independent companies.,"[('Croakun', 'PERSON')]"
Max Boon Camera Trainee,[]
"Ultimate Essence, Bringing luxury designer inspired fragrances into your car",[]
"Commercial photography, commercial video production, film production, and 
corporate video, Commercial Studio Johor Services Base in Johor, Kuala 
Lumpur, Singapore, provide world class services over international. At 
Unique Visual Production, we create the advertising photograph & film that 
grow sales & create brand awareness, and we know how to use creativity to 
deliver powerful ad messages.","[('Johor', 'LOCATION'), ('Services', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Johor, Kuala \r\nLumpur, Singapore', 'LOCATION'), ('Unique Visual Production', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Longhouse is a contemporary design atelier in the high end residential and 
hospitality sectors with a focus on decorative light fixtures. Handmade 
wood, metal, and rope parts combined with studio blown glass create their 
collections with locations in Napa, California and Brooklyn New York.","[('Napa', 'LOCATION'), ('California', 'LOCATION'), ('Brooklyn New York', 'LOCATION')]"
CAMELOT WELLNESS - Fitness Pilates Yoga Beauty,"[('CAMELOT WELLNESS', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Your business technology should be simple and reliable so you have more time to grow your business and achieve your goals. Let’s make it simple.,[]
"Carrum Downs favourite with great food restaurant & bar offering karaoke, 
kids play areas, free WiFi & much more. Make a reservation now!","[('Carrum Downs', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Located in Farnborough, we can manage commercial construction and renovation projects in Guildford and all nearby areas. Call 0203 432 2480 for more details.","[('Farnborough', 'LOCATION'), ('Guildford', 'LOCATION'), ('0203 432 2480', 'OTHER')]"
"<meta name= ""Keywords"" content = Local handyman, Member BBB,No job too small, Handyman services, Affordable handyman, Home maintenance, Home repairs, Handyman of Phoenix, Handyman Tempe, handyman, handyman Glendale, Handyman Scottsdale, Home care, Residential maintenance, Air conditioning service, Stucco repairs, Plumbing repairs, Electrical, Drywall repairs>","[('Phoenix', 'LOCATION'), ('Tempe', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Glendale', 'LOCATION'), ('Scottsdale', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
SmartyAds is a full stack programmatic ad buying company which offers the best-in-class profitable ad monetization and media buying solutions for advertisers and publishers in the digital marketing industry,"[('SmartyAds', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('full stack', 'QUANTITY')]"
"Brindle redefines the must have plugins for WordPress, only ours leave the competition in the dust. FREE Trial and Support plan included.","[('Brindle', 'TITLE'), ('WordPress', 'TITLE')]"
"10+ years experience. $24M in client revenue generated. Full-stack team of experts. Track record in eCommerce, SaaS, B2B, online courses and more.","[('10+ years', 'QUANTITY'), ('$24M', 'QUANTITY')]"
"location , shop pics and products. bongs , pipes and more",[]
"Professional Pool Repair - San Francisco Bay Area, Marin County","[('San Francisco Bay Area', 'LOCATION'), ('Marin County', 'LOCATION')]"
"Aerial videography and professional, independent film for commercial, creative, and business outlets.",[]
The Ruby + Associates team designs and engineers exceptional solutions to the world's most challenging structural engineering projects.,"[('Ruby + Associates', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
SEE IT. TASTE IT. BELIEVE IT. The next generation of plant based foods is here. Using plants to create delicious and satisfying meat experiences you crave.,[]
"We are a women's magazine on all things body and mind. Get the latest on life, love, fitness, personal care, nutrition and more! Welcome to Body + Mind!","[('Body', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Mind', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Happy Fortune is a family owned business with 40 years of experience in authentic family Chinese food in Dover. They offer appetizers, fried rice, and seafood.","[('Happy Fortune', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('40 years', 'QUANTITY'), ('Chinese', 'OTHER'), ('Dover', 'LOCATION')]"
The Employee Survey Company - Measure What Matters Most. Take Our Demo & Learn How Effective Employee Surveys Can Boost Engagement With Expert Analysis And Benchmark Data.,[]
"Exeter's leading Web, App and eCommerce development agency. Friendly team helping businesses transform ideas into experiences with innovative technologies.","[('Exeter', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"GLASSCON GmbH is a german premium facade contractor with subsidiaries & partners worldwide. GLASSCON offers worldwide from one hand full integrated ""turn key"" building envelopes, facade systems, curtain walls, facade engineering.","[('GLASSCON GmbH', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('german', 'OTHER'), ('GLASSCON', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('one', 'QUANTITY')]"
"GCT Marketing lives and breathes design and know that every property has a story, every space unique. Our tailored approach to luxury staging means we carefully curate high-end furniture, furnishings and accessories to suit the individual room and existing architecture.","[('GCT Marketing', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('every', 'QUANTITY'), ('space', 'QUANTITY')]"
Looking for High Speed Broadband Service in Punjab Dreamtel Provides you with the Best Broadband Service in Punjab. Unlimited Broadband Connection in Punjab.,"[('Punjab', 'LOCATION'), ('Dreamtel', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Punjab', 'LOCATION'), ('Punjab', 'LOCATION')]"
"Resource for professionals in the packaging industry- Information on packaging, bottling, sealing, cartoning, wrapping, multipacking and more",[]
"At AAK, we are experts in plant-based oils and fats. We collaborate with you in an innovative and sustainable way to come up with the optimal solution.","[('AAK', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
This is a hidden article.,[]
"Sterling Edge manufactures quality milling tools for 3D applications, primarily for the mold-and-die-making industry.","[('Sterling Edge', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Are you looking for LED Lighting in Australia? LED World is Australia's leading supplier for domestic and commercial lighting.,"[('Australia', 'LOCATION'), ('LED World', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Australia', 'LOCATION')]"
"Diamex, Inc. in New York, NY manufactures polished diamonds from rough, 
recuts and repairs stones of all sizes, buys and sells finished diamonds to 
both wholesalers and retailers while continuing to expand their services 
with new technologies and techniques. They provide jewelry consultations, 
appraisals and is a trusted resource for estate sales or private purchases.","[('Diamex, Inc.', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('New York, NY', 'LOCATION'), ('both', 'QUANTITY')]"
"Removals, delivery, logistics, moving house, ",[]
Cambridge Properties has consistently been at the forefront of the Arizona residential and commercial real estate market as a leader in luxury living.,"[('Cambridge Properties', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Arizona', 'LOCATION')]"
"Spacemaker enables teams to collaborate, analyse and design real estate sites, using AI to help developers, architects and planners to make better decisions, faster.","[('Spacemaker', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
The owner of this domain has not yet uploaded their website.,[]
Red Door Properties' ultimate goal in the business is creating customers (and friends!) for life; not quick transactional sales. Work with the team today!,"[('Red Door', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('today', 'DATE')]"
"Water Studio designs and builds contemporary water feature, water walls, and fire features for commercial, residential, and public spaces","[('Water Studio', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Southern Welding, from Industrial products to barn stalls to entrance gates, we have been in business since 1999 with over 30 years experience. Let us quote all your steel, aluminum, stainless steel, and all types of welding needs.","[('Southern Welding', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('1999', 'DATE'), ('over 30 years experience', 'QUANTITY')]"
We are merging all CPA Networks to provide a solution for you to optimize ads conversions and earn more with responsive landing pages.,"[('CPA', 'OTHER')]"
"A leader of Industrial Tool Rental in Eastern Canada. Offering Sales, Service, and Rental of tools for Pipe, Tube, Milling, Bolting, Cutting and Torque.","[('Eastern Canada', 'LOCATION')]"
"Cartiere Miliani Fabriano is a historic, yet modern business with characteristics that are unique in the paper mill world.","[('Cartiere Miliani Fabriano', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Buildia Constructions is based in Limassol and specializes in commercial, institutional, industrial, and civil construction services.","[('Buildia Constructions', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Limassol', 'LOCATION')]"
"Health, Nutrition, Tips & Tricks, Mini Cooper, Classic Car",[]
"Austin Business Listing of Austin, TX. Find a wide range of products and services offered from businesses in the Austin metro area.","[('Austin', 'LOCATION'), ('Austin, TX', 'LOCATION'), ('Austin', 'LOCATION')]"
The Vision Engine is a boutique agency specialising in helping service/experiential brands become both customer-centred and profitable. ,"[('Vision Engine', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
About us - information,[]
LBS Properties is a property development and investment company focused on the residential and commercial sectors of the Central London market.,"[('LBS Properties', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Central London', 'LOCATION')]"
"Bikers Studio is a top and well known Motorcycle and Bike Helmet Dealer in Odhav, Ahmedabad and also known for Helmet Dealers-axor. Get access to address, contact number, photos, directions, working hours and services of Bikers Studio, Odhav, Ahmedabad.","[('Bikers Studio', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Odhav, Ahmedabad', 'LOCATION'), ('Dealers-axor', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Bikers Studio', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Odhav, Ahmedabad', 'LOCATION')]"
"Amber Education Services Ltd. offers workforce development services to Victoria, Nanaimo, Parksville, Port Alberni, Ucluelet, Tofino and Campbell River.","[('Amber Education Services Ltd.', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Victoria', 'LOCATION'), ('Nanaimo', 'LOCATION'), ('Parksville', 'LOCATION'), ('Port Alberni', 'LOCATION'), ('Ucluelet', 'LOCATION'), ('Tofino', 'LOCATION'), ('Campbell River', 'LOCATION')]"
Prestigious and Affordable Luxury Watches. Elegance does not have to break the bank!,[]
MyDreamFurniture is the best furniture review blog you will come across. Get frequent updates and comprehensive reviews about the top and best furniture for home.,"[('MyDreamFurniture', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"YouBuy Online Shopping - Great deals on a huge range of products including Homewares, Furniture, Camping and Outdoors, Fitness Accessories, Pet Supplies, Tools, Truck Parts, plus much, much more. Purchase Online Now!","[('YouBuy', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Vapor Boss is retail vape shop, both online and brick and mortar locations, providing the vape community with quality vapes, E-liquids, E-juice, salt nic, and more.","[('Vapor Boss', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Affordable powered access hire across South Wales, Bristol and Gloucester. No Account Needed - Hire Today","[('South Wales', 'LOCATION'), ('Bristol', 'LOCATION'), ('Gloucester', 'LOCATION'), ('Today', 'DATE')]"
Fill and submit the online contact form and we will get back to you as soon as possible. You can also reach us by Calling 1-888-801-4645.,"[('1-888-801-4645', 'OTHER')]"
"Professional Cosmetic Tattooing in Moonee Ponds specialising in eyeliner, feather touch or 3D eyebrows and Lips shading.","[('Moonee Ponds', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Professional landscaping solutions<br>Pattern Imprinted Concrete by Readypave Ltd creates the ultimate first impression for your Driveway, Patio, Path, Pool surround or Roadway. Quality assured. Available in a range of colours and patterns.","[('Readypave Ltd', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('first impression', 'QUANTITY')]"
"provide cleaning and janitorial services to every sector of the business community which includes retail, manufacturing, warehousing and office based companies in malaysia.","[('every', 'QUANTITY'), ('malaysia', 'LOCATION')]"
"Fort Myers General Contractor | Commercial Construction services in SW Florida | Healthcare, Commercial, Hostpitality, Retail and Marine industry.","[('Fort Myers', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('SW Florida', 'LOCATION')]"
Responsive WordPress Gym Fitness Theme,"[('WordPress', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Delivering solutions around the world!,[]
"LC Resources is a leader in innovative HPLC software, HPLC training, and contract laboratory services for HPLC and LC-MS. Look to LC Resources for the expertise, knowledge, and experience you need to solve your most vexing chromatography problems.","[('LC Resources', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('HPLC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('HPLC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('HPLC', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('LC Resources', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Ace Industries: Cranes, Hoists, Come Alongs,  Gantry Cranes, Jib Cranes, Davit Cranes, Winches, End Trucks, Lifting Slings and Bridge Cranes","[('Ace', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
International TOC Consulting Group,"[('TOC Consulting Group', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Experienced Motion Designer with a demonstrated history of working in the media production industry. Skilled in Broadcasting, Graphics, Video and Animation Arts",[]
"Hi I'm Lenore, I'm a travel OT. I blog about my experiences during my travels, share personal stories, tips, tricks, and itineraries.","[('Lenore', 'PERSON')]"
Collector of alternative styles of living.,[]
SHAPA has been the UK's leading specialist association for the Solids Handling and Processing Industry since its formation in 1981.,"[('SHAPA', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('UK', 'LOCATION'), ('Solids Handling and Processing Industry', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('1981', 'DATE')]"
"A&M Communication, the best advertising and digital marketing company in Ranchi. Our services included Digital marketing, Advertising, Communication, Branding, Social Media Promotion, Public Relation.","[('A&M Communication', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Ranchi', 'LOCATION')]"
">Check for available units at Falcon Bridge at Gale Ranch in San Ramon, CA. View floor plans, photos, and community amenities. Make Falcon Bridge at Gale Ranch your new home.","[('Falcon Bridge', 'LOCATION'), ('Gale', 'LOCATION'), ('Ranch', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('San Ramon, CA.', 'LOCATION'), ('Falcon Bridge', 'LOCATION'), ('Gale', 'LOCATION'), ('Ranch', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"D.G Pictures offers professional video production services including Wedding Film Production, Live theatre/stage event coverage and corporate productions.","[('D.G Pictures', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
BigFuture is a Sydney based development team with extensive financial expertise.,"[('BigFuture', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Sydney', 'LOCATION')]"
"Impa Software is an emerging IT Service and solution provider in Malaysia, which includes ERP software like Ship chandler, Web Design, SEO, & etc..","[('Impa Software', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Malaysia', 'LOCATION'), ('Ship chandler', 'OTHER')]"
Republic of Coffee Specialty Roasters Roasting and supplying coffee since 2011. Our passion is for everything coffee. Sourcing the best ethically sourced beans is important to us. We are constantly improving ourselves ensuring the beans and coffee products we sell are nothing short of amazing.,"[('Republic of Coffee', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('2011', 'DATE')]"
"Orlando General Contractor, Building Contractor, commercial contractor, residential contractor, licensed Florida contractor, Orlando,Fl, bathroom contractor, kitchen contractor, remodel contractor, home additions, home renovations, water, fire and smoke restoration, reconstruction, insurance repairs, insurance contractor Clermont, Fl","[('Orlando', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Florida', 'LOCATION'), ('Orlando', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Fl', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Clermont', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Fl', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"K R Industries is a Leading Custom Molded Rubber Parts Products Manufacturers in India,USA specializing in all types of Molded Rubber Parts,Rubber Bonded with Child Parts (Metal). Contact us!","[('K R Industries', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('India,USA', 'LOCATION')]"
"KECO CAPITAL was formed by investors to serve investors. Founders, Kekoa and Cory, envisioned a full-service lending company serving new and seasoned investors. Whether they are funding a single family renovation or a new construction hotel, they are passionate about offering their expertise to build long-lasting relationships.","[('KECO CAPITAL', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Kekoa', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Cory', 'PERSON'), ('single family', 'QUANTITY')]"
"Cottage Cafe is a restaurant with classic breakfast or lunch that will bust your belly, but not your budget. ","[('Cottage Cafe', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"TaoMylife集运
TaoMylife International Logistics Ltd.","[('TaoMylife集运', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('TaoMylife International Logistics Ltd.', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Providing innovative engineering and manufacturing solutions since 1963, Control Devices offers products and components for pressure washers, air compressors, fire suppression systems, vehicle systems, specialty gas applications, and the agricultural and food & beverage industries. Specific products include a wide variety of specialty valves, nozzles, and condensate traps.","[('1963', 'DATE')]"
Sparrow Technologies - IT services VOIP Internet Phone CCTV Voip Cat5 cat6 network cabling cctv wireless remote support,"[('Sparrow Technologies', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Cat5', 'OTHER'), ('cat6', 'OTHER')]"
"Energy Wise Solutions has a Heat Storm Heating Line and North Storm Cooling line of products that vary from portable air conditioners, to window mounted air conditioners, to indoor infrared space heaters, to radiant glass heaters, to wall heaters to outdoor infrared heaters.","[('Energy Wise Solutions', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Buy, Sell and Services",[]
"Systems Associates manufactures weighing and identification systems primarily for the railroad transportation industry. We also manufacture numeric displays to show weight, time, product count, etc.","[('Systems Associates', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"<br>Royal Capital Ltd., no 1 retail broker in Bangladesh.
 RCL is well accepted to his clients for its futuristic thinking and innovative services.
","[('Royal Capital Ltd.', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('no 1 retail broker', 'QUANTITY'), ('Bangladesh', 'LOCATION'), ('RCL', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Planning to move to Malaysia? We sponsor foreigners to stay in Malaysia as a second home for their family to enjoy quality lifestyle.,"[('Malaysia', 'LOCATION'), ('Malaysia', 'LOCATION'), ('second home', 'QUANTITY')]"
"Facials in New York City that are customized to fit each individual’s skin 
needs. Unlike other spa facials, MiCara focuses on understanding your 
specific requirements to provide treatments that will deliver beautiful 
skin.","[('New York City', 'LOCATION'), ('each individual', 'QUANTITY'), ('MiCara', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"American Pipe Fitting Manufacturer of bushings, caps, plugs, and couplings","[('American', 'OTHER')]"
"Overseas Printing Corporation has been recognized as a leader amongst international commercial  book printing companies. 
Overseas Printing offers complete pre-press, printing, and bindery facilities.","[('Overseas Printing Corporation', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Overseas Printing', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Sunglo supplies Fruit, Natural and Greek Yoghurt, Lassi, Sour Cream to Peninsular Malaysia, Sabah and Sarawak. Contact us on 1800 888 YOG","[('Sunglo', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Malaysia', 'LOCATION'), ('Sabah', 'LOCATION'), ('Sarawak', 'LOCATION'), ('1800 888 YOG', 'OTHER')]"
Contact with an owner of mergeskills.com domain name.,"[('mergeskills.com', 'OTHER')]"
"Trans World Metals, LTD has been in the precious metals business for 34 years and since 1986 has been a worldwide broker/dealer in precious metals, includling gold, silver, palladium and platinum bullion and gold and silver-backed IRA's. Based in Kailua Kona, Hawaii.","[('Trans World Metals, LTD', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('34 years', 'QUANTITY'), ('1986', 'DATE'), ('Kailua Kona, Hawaii', 'LOCATION')]"
"Increase sales and deliver effortless customer care with multi-channel messaging, smart campaigns, and chatbots. -",[]
"Alpha Approach is a premium end-to-end career counselling platform, helping students accelerate and land dream jobs across consulting and banking. Supported by experienced industry professionals from top tier firms in the UK. ","[('Alpha Approach', 'TITLE'), ('UK', 'LOCATION')]"
Beach Boutique is SurfGirl’s online shop with a difference! It’s a treasure chest of beach essentials and handmade crafts for girls who love the ocean.,"[('Beach Boutique', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('SurfGirl', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Buy now at AM-AutoParts! Always Free Shipping. Order by 4 P.M. EST and your order ships same day.,"[('AM-AutoParts', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('4 P.M. EST', 'DATE')]"
This domain may be for sale!,[]
"Yuen Mei is a Chinese takeaway in Torbay. Visit us at 51 Market St, Torquay, Torbay, TQ1 3AW or call 01803 294 497 for orders and more information.","[('Yuen', 'LOCATION'), ('Mei', 'PERSON'), ('Chinese', 'OTHER'), ('Torbay', 'LOCATION'), ('51 Market St, Torquay', 'LOCATION'), ('Torbay', 'LOCATION'), ('TQ1 3AW', 'LOCATION'), ('01803 294 497', 'OTHER')]"
Interconnect Solutions Company (ISC) partners with you to design & manufacture complex product solutions & custom overmolded assemblies. Let’s get started.,"[('Interconnect Solutions Company', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('ISC', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Largest wealth management firm in Lamorinda (Lafayette, Moraga and Orinda, CA). We are a 100% fee-only fiduciary. Retirement planning, financial planning & investment management services. Experienced, credentialed financial advisors. 35+ years in business. Call 925.299.1500 for a free, no-obligation portfolio review.","[('Lamorinda', 'LOCATION'), ('Lafayette', 'LOCATION'), ('Moraga', 'LOCATION'), ('Orinda, CA', 'LOCATION'), ('100%', 'QUANTITY'), ('35+ years', 'QUANTITY'), ('925.299.1500', 'OTHER')]"
"Increase growth, reduce risk, accelerate impact - Pottinger provides strategic and financial advice that stands the test of time",[]
Eco Green Park is your premier option for secure document shredding and record storage services. We can handle large quantities of documents. Call today for trustworthy service!,"[('Eco Green Park', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('today', 'DATE')]"
we are a company dedicated to the wholesale and retail of electronic and wireless products. www.spherewebsite.com,"[('www.spherewebsite.com', 'OTHER')]"
"Esteem Homes LLC offers custom residential properties. Our company is 
designed to help you achieve your dream of living in a beautiful home. 
Imagine having an amazing space in which you are able to entertain friends 
and family, be close to all local shopping and dining, and unwind from a 
long day.","[('Esteem Homes LLC', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
TEG Solutions provides clients an economic and environmentally safe way to ensure the longevity of their Dehydration Units and BTEX Condensers.,"[('TEG Solutions', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('BTEX', 'OTHER')]"
Caterers in Kent & Sussex - Cuisine Studio Catering Co offer bespoke Event Catering & Event Management. Caterers using high quality produce from local farms,"[('Kent', 'LOCATION'), ('Sussex', 'LOCATION'), ('- Cuisine Studio Catering Co', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Home: Shine Live is a charitable organisation developed to support secondary schools and young people through the delivery of their SMSC curriculum and creative gatherings.,"[('Home', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Shine Live', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
JA specialises in insuring High Value and High Risk Industries.,"[('JA', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
We are a leading regional multinational pharmaceutical company with over 50 years of experience in the pursuit of health and wellbeing.,"[('over 50 years', 'QUANTITY')]"
Brazilian agriculture and agrochemicals strategy design and consulting firm. ,"[('Brazilian', 'OTHER')]"
"Asis 2000 and Asis@NZ Limited are reputable management, training and BPO 
companies. Collaborating closely with our customers, we develop and execute 
long-term strategies to achieve the desired performance and keeping the 
costs low for our customers.","[('Asis 2000', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Asis@NZ Limited', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Based in Austin TX, Magdesign serves high-tech and startups with graphic design, branding, UI/UX and traditional print design for seamless, consistent visual communications.","[('Austin TX', 'LOCATION'), ('Magdesign', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Celebrating the Malaysia's Most Attractive Graduate Employer Brands To Work For, 100% Voted for by University Students across Malaysia.","[('Malaysia', 'LOCATION'), ('100%', 'QUANTITY'), ('Malaysia', 'LOCATION')]"
"Premium Home and Commercial Construction and Renovation by B.H. Builders, Inc.","[('B.H. Builders, Inc.', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Trucking Company that is ethical and fair to drivers in pay, choose schedule. www.tctlogisticstn.com","[('www.tctlogisticstn.com', 'OTHER')]"
"Established in 1981, ST Auto Spares Sdn. Bhd. has more than 30 years of experience in auto spare parts & accessories trading in Malaysia. Find genuine Toyota, Lexus, Isuzu, Mazda parts at ST Auto Spares!","[('1981', 'DATE'), ('ST Auto Spares Sdn. Bhd.', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('more than 30 years', 'QUANTITY'), ('Malaysia', 'LOCATION'), ('Toyota', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Lexus', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Isuzu', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Mazda', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('ST Auto Spares', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Kahi Classifieds Post Free Buy Sell Ad Posting Sites Online. Search Classified Ads For Jobs, Local business directory, Find Real Estate Properties On Sale & More.","[('Kahi', 'PERSON')]"
BL Logistics provides custom surface transportation solutions to fit every operation's transportation needs.,"[('BL Logistics', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('every operation', 'QUANTITY')]"
Massachusetts Wealth Management manages client assets to the individual need of clients.,"[('Massachusetts Wealth Management', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Web and mobile apps development in the heart of sunny Marbella.,"[('Marbella', 'LOCATION')]"
"Real Estate Asset Management & Development, Portfolio, Office, Shopping Center, Industrial-Logistics, Hotels and Hospitality, Residential Multifamily and single, Student Housing, Senior Living, Mixed-Use",[]
UKB Marketing specialises in creating high-quality digital marketing campaigns that attract scores of customers and generate more sales.,"[('UKB Marketing', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('scores of', 'QUANTITY')]"
"Monadelphous is a leading Australian engineering group providing construction, maintenance and industrial services to the resources, energy and infrastructure sectors. We are involved in some of Australia’s biggest and most complex projects.","[('Monadelphous', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Australian', 'LOCATION'), ('Australia', 'LOCATION')]"
Artboard 1 Copy 103Created with Sketch. Brandbee is a technology and digital marketing company with our HQ in the heart of Stockholm. Everything we do is based…,"[('Artboard', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('1 Copy 103Created', 'COMMERCIAL_ITEM'), ('Brandbee', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Stockholm', 'LOCATION')]"
Canvas Printing For Photos & Artist: Canvas Guide,[]
Technology Research and Development,[]
Asian Fusion restaurant on the landing in Fort Wayne,"[('Asian', 'OTHER'), ('Fort Wayne', 'LOCATION')]"
"UK supplier of healthcare care technology and alert systems for a wide range of industries, including; staff attack, nurse call and critical communication.","[('UK', 'LOCATION')]"
Golden Shine is a domestic referral cleaning agency that specializes in house cleaning and carpet cleaning throughout San Diego and surrounding areas.,"[('Golden Shine', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('San Diego', 'LOCATION')]"
Visual Communication & Brand Design,[]
"RESORT CONSULTANTS Tropical Area is a consultancy specialised in resort concept and development, including  preliminary and feasibility studies, architecture, interior and furniture design, project management and procurement  .Tropical Area is and has been involved in numerous resorts projects ,often very early in the process , developing new hospitality concepts or identifying locations. We made a specialty of developments in remote locations, with strong emphasis on the respect of the environment.","[('RESORT CONSULTANTS', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Tropical', 'LOCATION'), ('Area', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Area', 'LOCATION')]"
BERTEN provides wireless communication systems and crypto security products for critical platforms.,"[('BERTEN', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Classic Brands is a leader of specialty sleep products and leather furniture sold in store chains nationwide and globally online. Learn more here.,"[('Classic Brands', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Check out this GoDaddy hosted webpage! http://sparkisys.com.,"[('GoDaddy', 'TITLE'), ('http://sparkisys.com', 'OTHER')]"
The owner of this domain has not yet uploaded their website.,[]
"Embedded Computer Design, Assembly, Branding, Supply Chain & Lifecycle Management. Utilize our expertise to craft solutions that fulfill your needs.",[]
A corporate Bootstrap theme by Medium Rare,[]
LearningApps - interactive and multimedia learning blocks,[]
"Carbine Media Year Planners can be used on a wall, desk or door & provide professional people with a medium to see the entire working year at a glance.","[('Carbine', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Media', 'TITLE'), ('Planners', 'COMMERCIAL_ITEM'), ('entire working year', 'QUANTITY')]"
A creative agency working with cultural organisations and commercial brands,[]
"Fasteners and Construction Supplies New Orleans, LA www.acefasteners.com (504) 738-1384","[('New Orleans, LA', 'LOCATION'), ('www.acefasteners.com', 'OTHER'), ('(504) 738-1384', 'OTHER')]"
"ImaBiotech offers a unique Spatial Multi-omics Platform including Mass Spectrometry Imaging and Spatial transcriptomics to provide deep drug evaluation in preclinical and clinical studies. Our offer includes Biomarker discovery, DMPK, Pharmacology, Toxicity, ADME and PK/PD: solutions from Lead Optimization to Phase III. ","[('ImaBiotech', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('DMPK', 'OTHER'), ('ADME', 'OTHER'), ('PK/PD', 'OTHER'), ('Phase', 'OTHER'), ('III.', 'QUANTITY')]"
"SAFFANA's expression is a playground for boundless creativity, channeling contemporary fashion concepts for modern day women. We at SAFFANA believe that a mix of feminine and flirty vogue trend is an effortless way of expressing a good taste","[('SAFFANA', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('SAFFANA', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"CMR Construction serves the greater South Florida and Miami metropolitan area. We build functional, beautiful spaces for Florida's most discerning people.","[('CMR Construction', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('South Florida', 'LOCATION'), ('Miami', 'LOCATION'), ('Florida', 'LOCATION')]"
"Jamesport Farm Brewery is a pet friendly microbrewery and tasting room situated on an immaculate, active 43-acre farm nestled in the heart of eastern Long Island’s North Fork wine country.","[('Jamesport Farm Brewery', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('43-acre', 'QUANTITY'), ('eastern Long Island', 'LOCATION'), ('North Fork', 'LOCATION')]"
"EARTHFOOD’s is a leading organic store of healthy, nutritious foods. Get pure and natural ghee, honey, spices, powders, and much more at reasonable prices.","[('EARTHFOOD', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
P&S Pest Control Inc. is a family owned and operated pest control company providing quality service using the highest quality products. We are fully licensed and insured with over 23 years in business. ,"[('P&S Pest Control Inc.', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('over 23 years', 'QUANTITY')]"
"APL Industries Rajkot, Gujarat, India Cement Pipe Machinery & Plants, Paver Machinery Plant, Cement Block & Fly Ash Bricks Machinery, Split Pulley, Cement Articles Equipments, Hydraulic Press For Pavers","[('APL Industries Rajkot', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Gujarat,', 'LOCATION'), ('India', 'LOCATION')]"
"Arcon Contracting | A leader in general construction, renovation, design build, and construction management services","[('Arcon Contracting', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
CSI Capital provides alternative funding and financing for small and middle market businesses in Denver Colorado,"[('CSI Capital', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Denver Colorado', 'LOCATION')]"
The owner of this domain has not yet uploaded their website.,[]
"CloudBooks is a small business bookkeeping & invoice software. We help you in time tracking, business expense management & creating unlimited professional invoices.","[('CloudBooks', 'TITLE')]"
"Bali's leading ECO manufacturer for startups & established brands for premium grade swimwear, active, lounge & coverups. Your handover priced in 3 days.","[('Bali', 'LOCATION'), ('3 days', 'QUANTITY')]"
"My WordPress Blog<br>For Best AC Repair service Bhubaneswar , Ac Reail and engineering services in bhubaneswar call us on 9938083943.","[('WordPress', 'TITLE'), ('Bhubaneswar', 'LOCATION'), ('Ac Reail', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('bhubaneswar', 'LOCATION'), ('9938083943', 'OTHER')]"
"It's Fresh, It's Healthy!",[]
"Zed Services is a Workers’ Compensation consultant and helps clients with Workers’ Compensation refunds and Workers’ Compensation premium recovery. We are known for our response rate, customer commitment, and attention to detail, and have immense respect for our customers. We serve clients nationwide. Learn more.","[('Zed Services', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"City Car Care is an authorized Bosch car service centre in Delhi, located at Kirti Nagar. We offer all type of car repair and maintenance services as a Bosch Auto Service Center Delhi.","[('City Car Care', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Bosch', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Delhi', 'LOCATION'), ('Kirti Nagar', 'LOCATION'), ('Bosch Auto Service Center', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Delhi', 'LOCATION')]"
"CCNA offer innovative design, development, and implementation of converged Voice, Video, Application, and Data solutions.","[('CCNA', 'TITLE')]"
"123Link - Best URL Shortener To Earn Money 2021 - 123link.co. Earn money on short links. Make short links and earn the biggest money. Short Links and Earn Money - Shorten, Share and Earn Money","[('123Link', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('2021', 'DATE'), ('123link.co', 'OTHER')]"
Florida Full Service Ship Chandler,"[('Florida', 'LOCATION'), ('Chandler', 'PERSON')]"
"Golden Season Pte Ltd, manufacturers of military rescue equipment, folding stretchers, combat ration packs, mobile shelter systems, military batteries and humanitarian relief products.","[('Golden Season Pte Ltd', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Curated for the discerning – discover the latest and best in luxe travel, dining, lifestyle and more",[]
"Primera Solutions designs, develops and deploys high value technology solutions for financial markets clients.","[('Primera Solutions', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"PM Solutions - Say Hello to your Customers. Services include direct mail, hybrid mail, postage, print, data services, creative and marketing Comments Feed",[]
Rising Edge offers consulting services and software development for automated testing and process control system applications,"[('Rising Edge', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Space Matrix is a global design & build firm that creates award-winning corporate workplaces that inspires people and impacts business,"[('Space Matrix', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Let your hair show the world who you really are. Like a piece of art, your hair is a canvas waiting to share your own expression and style. Come achieve the",[]
Statstics and Data Science Contractor,[]
"MIBS TECH is an innovative product development company located in Bangalore, India. The company developing single board computer modules called 'PC-on-chip' and highly integrated SBCs for embedded systems and Application and also developing Home Automation Products. Highly focused towards Quality of Products. Support customer demand and maintain a good relationship with customer.","[('MIBS TECH', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Bangalore, India', 'LOCATION'), ('single board', 'QUANTITY')]"
"Hardin & Sons Serves Seattle, Tacoma, Olympia, Kent, Auburn, Lakewood, Renton, Edgewood & Kirkland, Washington.","[('Hardin & Sons', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Seattle', 'LOCATION'), ('Tacoma', 'LOCATION'), ('Olympia', 'LOCATION'), ('Kent', 'LOCATION'), ('Auburn', 'LOCATION'), ('Lakewood', 'LOCATION'), ('Renton', 'LOCATION'), ('Edgewood', 'LOCATION'), ('Kirkland', 'LOCATION'), ('Washington', 'LOCATION')]"
University Village – Exclusively Bumble and bumble,"[('University Village', 'LOCATION')]"
"Business and Personal Contract Hire and Finance Leasing. Ask us about Mileage Rebates and Damage Waivers. Contract Hire, Finance Lease, BCH, PCH, Part Exchange Welcome",[]
"Innovation, flexible solutions shaped with immense passion.",[]
"Creative Digital Design Studio based in Norwich, UK. Low cost web design and development, logo and graphic design, and social media management for small businesses","[('Creative Digital Design Studio', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Norwich, UK', 'LOCATION')]"
"Welcome to your one stop filtration specialist. We sell oil, fuel, air and water filters from Donaldson, Mann, Stanadyne and many other brands. We also sell filter accessories.","[('one', 'QUANTITY'), ('Donaldson', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Mann', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Stanadyne', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
A New Season & New Times are Coming! Thanks to all the loyal clients and brand new clients that have supported us through this crazy year. We are thankful and excited for some new changes that will be happening at ruby salon! We are recreating ourselves in the future and excited to share with … Continue reading,"[('year', 'DATE'), ('ruby salon', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"VK is the largest European social network with more than 100 million active users. Our goal is to keep old friends, ex-classmates, neighbors and colleagues in touch.","[('VK', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('European', 'LOCATION'), ('more than 100 million', 'QUANTITY'), ('users', 'QUANTITY')]"
Universal Minds Sdn Bhd (UMSB) is a consulting firm and a corporate development & training program provider in Malaysia. HRDF Claimable!,"[('Universal Minds Sdn Bhd', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('UMSB', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Malaysia', 'LOCATION'), ('HRDF', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Netcentric builds digital experiences that connect our clients to their customers. Our integrated partnerships with brands enable them to access the full potential of the Adobe Experience Cloud. ,"[('Netcentric', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Adobe', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Experience Cloud', 'TITLE')]"
The Official Website of the City Government of Calamba.<br>The Official Website of the City of Calamba.,"[('City Government of Calamba', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Calamba', 'LOCATION')]"
"RFM Construction Products (M) Sdn Bhd leading brands, Ramset and Statheros, offer a comprehensive range of products comprising mechanical and chemical anchors, fasteners, power tools and construction chemicals.","[('RFM Construction Products (M) Sdn Bhd', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"GET AS MANY LEADS, CLIENTS & CUSTOMERS AS YOU CAN HANDLE","[('MANY LEADS', 'QUANTITY'), ('CLIENTS', 'QUANTITY'), ('CUSTOMERS', 'QUANTITY')]"
The owner of this domain has not yet uploaded their website.,[]
Premier scuba diving & snorkeling excursions to Catalina Island in the Dominican Republic. Come and experience a true taste of paradise & relaxation!,"[('Catalina Island', 'LOCATION'), ('Dominican Republic', 'LOCATION')]"
Things to do in a city recommended by locals. Find the best prices for booking flights & hotels for your travels,[]
 High Touch Network -  ,[]
"Maverick is an interior design company with a unique signature elegance that resonates across a wide range of styles. We strive to create truly imaginative spaces that are both tastefully creative and invitingly livable. Home rennovation, development, and custom design. Live beautifully.","[('Maverick', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('both', 'QUANTITY')]"
"Blueprint Projects are local RIBA chartered architects based in Hythe Kent, 
servicing residential and commercial architecture projects throughout Kent 
& London.","[('Blueprint Projects', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('RIBA', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Hythe Kent', 'LOCATION'), ('Kent', 'LOCATION'), ('London', 'LOCATION')]"
"We connect Northeast farmers and eaters to an ethical, sustainable, regional food system, bringing you fresh, locally grown fruits and vegetables.","[('Northeast', 'LOCATION')]"
Accounting Services Bookkeeping services Outsourcing Accounting E-commerce Accounting GST Return Accounting Services Export Accounting,[]
"JDGlobal LLC Manufacturer's Representatives, Sales and Program Management","[('JDGlobal LLC', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Sasa Marketing is a marketing consultancy for SMEs, based in East Anglia and managed by Catherine Bowyer. With 25 years of marketing experience, her hands on approach will benefit any small enterprise looking to grow their business through quality marketing activity.","[('Sasa Marketing', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('East Anglia', 'LOCATION'), ('Catherine Bowyer', 'PERSON'), ('25 years', 'QUANTITY')]"
Acme International provides our customers with reliable access to exclusive designer brand named products for wholesalers and resellers.,"[('Acme International', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
non profit organization catering to underprivileged/underrepresented communities and youth to provide resources and empowerment.,[]
"Fabricor is a well established company, internationally known as an industry leader for solid surface and stone fabrication. From residential kitchens to extremely sophisticated fabrication and cladding, Fabricor is the one source with the experience and know-how to exceed expectations for your project.","[('Fabricor', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Fabricor', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('one source', 'QUANTITY')]"
"MEGA STAGE specializes in the SALES & RENTAL of modular structures for the entertainement industry. We are a Canadian company, and no project is too big or too small to use any or all of the different MEGA products!","[('MEGA STAGE', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Canadian', 'LOCATION'), ('MEGA', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Custom homes, Custom Remodel, Quality Craftmanship",[]
"MJ Iron Works invests a significant amount of energy and effort into producing the creative and impactful work for our clients. As a small, family owner company we tailor to the needs of any budget. There is no need to put on hold your metal works project.","[('MJ Iron Works', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Talgra consults with people who want to create positive social and environmental change with their money through sustainable investing.,"[('Talgra', 'PERSON')]"
Business and Marketing Internet Consulting,[]
"Located in Nashville, Oasis Center helps young people in Middle Tennessee move into a happy, healthy and productive adulthood. Learn more about Oasis Center.","[('Nashville', 'LOCATION'), ('Oasis Center', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Middle Tennessee', 'LOCATION'), ('Oasis Center', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
Natural-icon web and graphic design,[]
"806-376-8221 – FREE quotes. Family-owned and operated business. Specializing in fabricated steel for commercial, industrial, and institutional buildings.","[('806-376-8221', 'OTHER')]"
We are doing some maintenance on our site. Please come back later.,[]
"Futures & Commodities Brokerage, Advisory, and Investment Management Services",[]
Redspark is a superior custom website and mobile application development company planning to convey the world-class mobile applications for Android & iOS. Connect with us.,"[('Redspark', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Android', 'TITLE'), ('iOS', 'TITLE')]"
"From an idea to a live software product, without a headache. High quality software development experts as part of your existing team.Mobile App Development.","[('team.Mobile', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Arcadia Acres located near Ironton is owned and operated by 
cheryl and Mike Floerchinger.","[('Arcadia', 'LOCATION'), ('Acres', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('Ironton', 'LOCATION'), ('cheryl', 'PERSON'), ('Mike Floerchinger', 'PERSON')]"
Your source for information on all Oracle Database error codes,"[('Oracle', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Sell your story to women's magazines & national newspapers for cash. Real life features, sold for great fees. Sell your story to publications with HotSpot Media.","[('HotSpot Media', 'ORGANIZATION')]"
"Upcoming IPOs, Recently Priced IPOs, IPO Calendars, IPO News, Pre-IPO institutional research and the Renaissance IPO ETFs - Renaissance Capital",[]
"Midwest Events provides online registrations for all your outdoor events in Minnesota, Wisconsin and Iowa.","[('Midwest', 'EVENT'), ('Events', 'ORGANIZATION'), ('all your outdoor events', 'QUANTITY'), ('Minnesota', 'LOCATION'), ('Wisconsin', 'LOCATION'), ('Iowa', 'LOCATION')]"
Are you looking for a one-stop-shop heating and cooling company in Bakersfield? You’ve come to the right place! We do heating & cooling and so much more!,"[('Bakersfield', 'LOCATION')]"
Make an offer on this domain and quickly take possession of it with a registrar of your choice.,[]
"Scoreboards, Scoring Tables, Digital and LED, High School Athletic Fundraising",[]
Shop powered by PrestaShop,"[('PrestaShop', 'TITLE')]"
"Providing IT sales and support in Fairbanks, Anchorage and all of Alaska. Workstation and server sales, installs, networking and consulting.","[('Fairbanks', 'LOCATION'), ('Anchorage', 'LOCATION'), ('Alaska', 'LOCATION')]"
